blueboxgrid.com 2012-06-23

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Statement sets forth Blue Box Group’s information gathering and dissemination practices regarding personal information collected by Blue Box Group directly from individuals (“you”) in connection with the website located at www.bluebox.net and related URLs (“Website”). 

Blue Box Group may collect various types of personal information from you in connection with the Website. Such data may include identifying information and contact information (names, titles, addresses, phone and fax numbers, and email addresses), financial and payment information, information about products and services ordered or provided, IP addresses, and other transaction-related data. 

### Contact Information

We may use personal information collected in connection with the Website to contact you regarding products or services you have ordered or are receiving, to send you information about Blue Box Group or its partners, to provide services to you, and for other purposes related to our business. You may choose to opt out of receiving communications from us. You will be given this choice at the points on the Website where we request your information. If you do not wish to receive future marketing mailings, please send an e-mail to privacy@bluebox.net. 

### Financial Information

We may ask you to provide your credit card or other financial account information to enable us to charge your account when you purchase services from us. All information you will be asked to provide is protected during transmission using SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) encryption to prevent it from being intercepted as it is transferred over the Internet. We provide this information only to third parties involved in processing payments for the services we provide and as otherwise provided in this Privacy Statement. 

### IP Addresses

We use your unique network address, or IP address, to help diagnose problems with our servers and to administer the Website. 

### Cookies

We may use cookies to keep track of your activities on the Website. We also use them to recognize return visitors and to track our promotions. 

### Disclosure Of Collected Information

Blue Box Group may disclose to third parties information we collect from you in connection with the Website (i) as necessary to provide services requested by you, (ii) as necessary to process payments, (iii) to our subcontractors, service providers and other agents in connection with the provision of services to you (provided such subcontractors and service providers are under a duty to maintain the confidentiality of such information), and (iv) in connection with requests from law enforcement officials, government agencies, or otherwise as required in connection with legal proceedings. In addition, we may transfer information we collect from you to a third party in connection with a merger or sale of our business or assets, in which case the resulting entity or transferee will be permitted to obtain and use such information subject to the terms of this Privacy Statement. 

### Contact

If you would like to contact Blue Box Group regarding the use of your personal information collected in connection with the Website, the types of third parties to whom we disclose such information, ways to limit the use and disclosure of such personal information, or to access, correct, amend, or delete your personal information collected in connection with the Website that is stored on our systems, please send an email to privacy@bluebox.net with your request. 

### Linked Sites

The Website contains links to external websites. Blue Box Group is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such third party websites. 

### Security

Blue Box Group implements industry-standard security measures designed to prevent the loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, destruction or alteration of the personal information we collect via the Website. 

### Updates

Blue Box Group may update this Privacy Statement from time to time to reflect changes in its services and customer feedback, and such changes shall become effective promptly after they are posted. Blue Box Group encourages you to periodically review this Privacy Statement to be informed of any changes. This Privacy Statement was last updated on July 14th, 2010. 

Blue Box Group, LLC complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries. Blue Box Group, LLC has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view our certification page, please visit [www.export.gov/safeharbor](http://www.export.gov/safeharbor)

In compliance with the US-EU and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles, Blue Box Group commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union or Swiss citizens with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact Blue Box Group at:

Blue Box Group, LLC  
c/o Complaints  
119 Pine Street, Suite 200  
Seattle, WA 98101

BlueBox has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the US-EU and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU SAFE HARBOR, operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed by Blue Box, please visit the [BBB EU SAFE HARBOR web site](http://www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints) for more information and to file a complaint.
